Finding Aid for School of Public Health (University of Michigan) Records 1909-2015 (bulk 1941-2006).
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Noreeen M. Clark, 1994-2004
  - Annual Files, 1996
    - Administration
      - Dean's Office
        - Staff, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Strategic Plans, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Associate Deans
          - Gray, Robert, 1996 (Box 72)
          - Schork, Tony, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Dean's Assistant, (Mark Becker), 1996 (Box 72)
      - Development Office
        - General, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Events
        - SPH Convocation, May 3, 1996 (Box 72)
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Faculty
        - Citrin, Toby, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Recruitment of James Tielsch, 1996 (Box 95)
      - General, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Memos to Faculty, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Research Council, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Students, 1996 (Box 95)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2076 ]
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Programs, 1996 (Box 96)
      - General, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1996 (Box 72)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Little, Roderick, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Maassab, John, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Epid Chair Search Committee, 1996 (Box 95)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Haefner, Don, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Israel, Barbara, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Wheeler, John, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 1996 (Box 73)
    - National
      - National Congress for Institutions Preparing Graduate Health Educators, Dallas, Texas, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service, 1996 (Box 73)
    - State
      - Michigan Initiative for Women's Health Symposium, Ann Arbor, Michigan, April 10, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Michigan Public Health Institute, Mount Pleasant, February 18, 1996 (Box 73)
    - University
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT), 1996 (Box 73)
      - Department of Research Development and Administration (DRDA), 1996 (Box 73)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Institute for Social Research, 1996 (Box 73)
      - International Institute, 1993-1996 (Box 73)
      - News Service, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Office of the President (James J. Duderstadt), 1996 (Box 73)
      - Office of the Provost, (J. Bernard Machen)
        - Annual Review Meeting, 1996 (Box 73)
        - General, 1996 (Box 73)
        - Information for Provost Machen, 1996 (Box 73)
      - Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Bob S. Holbrook), 1996 (Box 73)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research, (Homer A. Neal), 1996 (Box 73)
      - Office of the Vice Provost for Health Affairs, (Rhetaugh G. Dumas), 1996 (Box 73)
      - Regents, 1996 (Box 73)
  - Annual Files, 1997
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 1997 (Box 73)
        - General
          - A-E, 1997 (Box 73)
          - F-K, 1997 (Box 73)
          - L-Q, 1997 (Box 73)
          - R-Z, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Foreign, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Dean's Office
        - Associate Deans
          - Gray, Robert, 1997 (Box 96)
          - Schork, Tony, 1997 (Box 96)
        - Dean's Assistant, (Mark Becker), 1997 (Box 96)
      - Development Office
        - General, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Events
        - SPH Convocation, May 2, 1997 (Box 73)
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Faculty
        - Citrin, Toby, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Faculty Recruitment, 1997 (Box 96)
      - General, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Information Technology, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Memos to Faculty, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Students, 1997 (Box 96)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Programs, 1997 (Box 95)
      - Community-Based Public Health, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Executive Committee, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Research Council, 1997 (Box 73)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Little, Roderick, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Strategic Plan, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1997 (Box 73)
        - Kaplan, George
          - General, 1997 (Box 73)
          - Appointment, 1997 (Box 96)
        - Maassab, John, 1997 (Box 73)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education (Box 74)
        - General, 1997 (Box 74)
        - Haefner, Don, 1997 (Box 74)
        - Israel, Barbara, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1997 (Box 74)
        - Wessert, Bill, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 1997 (Box 74)
        - Hewlett Foundation Grant, 1997 (Box 74)
        - Human Nutrition Search, 1997 (Box 74)
        - Interdisciplinary Concentration in Population Planning and Family Health, 1997 (Box 74)
    - State
      - Michigan Initiative for Women's Health Symposium, Ann Arbor, Michigan, April 10, 1997 (Box 74)
    - University
      - Center for Health Services Research, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Center for Learning through Community Service, 1997 (Box 74)
      - General, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Information Technology Strategic Directions, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Institute of Gerontology, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Medical School, 1997 (Box 74)
      - News Service, 1997 (Box 74)
      - Office of the President (Lee Bollinger), 1997 (Box 74)
      - Office of the Provost, (Nancy Cantor), 1997 (Box 74)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Nancy Cantor), 1997 (Box 74)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs, (Gilbert S. Omenn), 1997 (Box 74)
      - Regents, 1997 (Box 74)
  - Annual Files, 1998
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Center on Race, Ethnicity, and Health, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Community-Based Public Health, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Concerning the Public Health, (discussion series), March 19, 1997; 1997-1998 (Box 74)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 1998 (Box 74)
        - General
          - A-E, 1998 (Box 74)
          - F-K, 1998 (Box 74)
          - L-Q, 1998 (Box 74)
          - R-Z, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Development Office
        - General, 1998 (Box 74)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 1998 (Box 74)
        - Dinner with Liz Wainstock re: Pfizer Cooperation, December 12, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Events
        - Public Health Symposium, Ann Arbor, September 29, 1998 (Box 74)
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, 1998 (Box 74)
      - Faculty (Box 75)
        - Alexander, Jeff, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Becker, Mark, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Citrin, Toby, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Gray, Robert, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Schork, Tony, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Recruitment, 1998 (Box 96)
      - General, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Memos to Faculty, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Prevention Research Center, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Public Health Information Services and Access, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Recruitment
        - Chase, Gary, 1998 (Box 96)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2028 ]
        - Folsom, Aaron, 1998 (Box 96)
        - Freed, Gary, 1998 (Box 96)
        - Taylor, Jeremy, 1998 (Box 96)
      - Students, 1998 (Box 96)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2073 ]
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Programs, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Executive Committee, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Futures Committee, 1998 (Box 75)
      - General, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Research Council, 1998 (Box 75)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Little, Roderick, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Meier, Peter, 1998 (Box 96)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2073 ]
        - Vincent, James, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Human Nutrition Program, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Kaplan, George (Box 75)
        - Economic Equity and Health of Populations, (meeting), June 4-6, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Subclinical Cardiovascular Disease Study, Site Visit, July 7, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Israel, Barbara, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Strecher, Vic, Health Media, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Wessert, Bill, 1998 (Box 75)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 1998 (Box 75)
        - International Health, 1998 (Box 75)
        - Zinn, Frank Population Planning Program (Box 75)
        - Interdisciplinary Concentration in Reproductive and Women's Health, 1998 (Box 75)
    - National (Box 76)
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service, 1998 (Box 76)
    - State
      - Michigan Association for Local Public Health, 1998 (Box 76)
    - University
      - Academic Program Group Research Subcommittee, 1998 (Box 76)
      - Community-Based Research Panel, 1998 (Box 76)
      - General, 1998 (Box 76)
      - Health Services Research Initiative, 1998 (Box 76)
      - Information Technology Strategic Directions, 1998 (Box 76)
      - Medical School, 1998 (Box 76)
      - News Service, 1998 (Box 76)
      - Office of the Provost, (Nancy Cantor) (Box 76)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Research, (Frederick C. Neidhaedrt), 1998 (Box 76)
      - Regents, 1998 (Box 76)
  - Annual Files, 1999
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 1999 (Box 76)
        - General
          - A-E, 1999 (Box 76)
          - F-K, 1999 (Box 76)
          - L-R, 1999 (Box 76)
          - S-Z, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Foreign, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Development Office
        - General, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Events
        - American University of Beirut Visit, February 22-26, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Public Health Symposium, Ann Arbor, September 13, 1999 (Box 76)
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, April 21, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Faculty
        - Citrin, Toby, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Gray, Robert, 1999 (Box 76)
      - General, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Memos to Faculty, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Prevention Research Center, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Recruitment
        - General, 1999 (Box 96)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2029 ]
        - Boehnke, Mike and Betsy Foxman, 1999 (Box 96)
      - Students, 1999 (Box 96)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2074 ]
    - Committees
      - Executive Committee, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1999 (Box 76)
      - General, 1999 (Box 76)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Little, Roderick, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Vincent, James, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1999 (Box 76)
        - Kaplan, George, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education (Box 77)
        - General, 1999 (Box 77)
        - Israel, Barbara, and Sherman James, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1999 (Box 77)
        - Media -- Faculty Public Relations, 1999 (Box 77)
        - Media and Public Health, 1999 (Box 77)
        - Wessert, Bill, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 1999 (Box 77)
        - Zinn, Frank Population Planning Program (Box 77)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service (includes National Institutes of Health and Environmental Protection Agency Correspondence), 1999 (Box 77)
    - State
      - Michigan Department of Community Health, 1999 (Box 77)
    - University
      - Academic Program Group, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Academic Program Group Research Subcommittee, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Center for Learning through Community Service, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Community-Based Research Panel, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Health Services Research Initiative, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Medical School, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Office of the Provost, (Nancy Cantor) (Box 77)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Nancy Cantor), 1999 (Box 77)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Research, (Fawwaz T. Ulaby), 1999 (Box 77)
      - Other Schools and Colleges, 1999 (Box 77)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1999 (Box 77)
      - Regents, 1999 (Box 77)
  - Annual Files, 2000
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 2000 (Box 77)
      - American Public Health Association, 2000 (Box 77)
      - Community-Based Public Health, 2000 (Box 77)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 2000 (Box 77)
        - General
          - A-E, 2000 (Box 77)
          - F-K, 2000 (Box 77)
          - L-Q, 2000 (Box 77)
          - R-Z, 2000 (Box 77)
        - Foreign, 2000 (Box 77)
      - Development Office
        - General, 2000 (Box 77)
        - Development Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 77)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 2000 (Box 77)
      - Events (Box 78)
        - Breadth Day, Public Health Genetics Symposium, September 18, 2000 (Box 78)
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, April 27, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Faculty
        - Alexander, Jeff, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Citrin, Toby, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Public Health Information Services and Access, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Prevention Research Center, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Recruitment
        - General, 2000 (Box 96)
        - Haan, Mary, 2000 (Box 96)
      - Students, 2000 (Box 96)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2075 ]
    - Committees
      - Executive Committee, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Faculty Meetings, 2000 (Box 78)
      - General, 2000 (Box 78)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Little, Roderick, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Vincent, James, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Martin, Jim, Radioactive Materials Safety, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Kaplan, George, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 2000 (Box 78)
        - James, Sherman, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Media -- Faculty Public Relations, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Wessert, Bill, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Interdepartmental Concentration in Genetics, 2000 (Box 78)
        - Population-Environment Dynamics Project, 2000 (Box 78)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service (includes Center for Disease Control correspondence), 2000 (Box 78)
    - University
      - Academic Program Group Research Subcommittee, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Cancer Center, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Center for Clinical Investigation and Therapeutics Advisory Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 78)
      - Institute for Social Research, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Medical School Development Advisory Committee Meeting, October 10, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Mentoring Retreat, November 6, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Office of the President, (Lee Bollinger), 2000 (Box 78)
      - Office of the Provost, (Nancy Cantor) (Box 78)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Nancy Cantor), 2000 (Box 78)
      - Office of the Executive Vice-President for Development, (Susan F. Feagin), 2000 (Box 78)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Research, (Fawwaz T. Ulaby), 2000 (Box 78)
      - Other Schools and Colleges, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Reproductive Sciences Program, 2000 (Box 78)
      - Regents, 2000 (Box 78)
  - Annual Files, 2001
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 2001 (Box 79)
      - American Public Health Association, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Community-Based Public Health, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 2001 (Box 79)
        - General
          - A-E, 2001 (Box 79)
          - F-K, 2001 (Box 79)
          - L-Q, 2001 (Box 79)
          - R-Z, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Foreign, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Development Office
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Events
        - Dr. James Haveman visit, November 15, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Public Health Symposium, October 26, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Faculty
        - Alexander, Jeff, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Gray, Robert, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Prevention Research Center, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Public Health Recruitment
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Haan, Mary, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Public Health Information Services and Access, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Recruitment, 2001 (Box 95)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2031 ]
      - Students, 2001 (Box 95)
    - Committees
      - Department Chair Meetings, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Executive Committee, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Faculty Meetings, 2001 (Box 79)
      - General, 2001 (Box 79)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Little, Roderick, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Chair Search, 2001 (Box 96)
        - Kalbfleisch, John, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Vincent, James, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Martin, Jim, Radioactive Materials Safety, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Kaplan, George, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - James, Sherman, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 2001 (Box 79)
        - Wessert, Bill, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 2001 (Box 79)
    - International
      - World Health Organization, 2001 (Box 79)
    - National
      - 3rd National Conference on Genetics and Disease Prevention, Ann Arbor, September 19-20, 2001 (Box 79)
    - State
      - General, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Michigan Public Health Association, 2001 (Box 79)
    - University
      - Division of Research Development and Administration, 2001 (Box 79)
      - General, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School, 2001 (Box 79)
      - Health Services Research Initiative, 2001 (Box 80)
      - Medical School, 2001 (Box 80)
      - Mentoring Retreat, November 6, 2001 (Box 80)
      - Office of the President, (Lee Bollinger), 2001 (Box 80)
      - Office of the Provost, (Nancy Cantor and Lisa A. Tedesco) (Box 80)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Nancy Cantor and Lisa A. Tedesco), 2001 (Box 80)
      - Office of the Executive Vice-President for Development, (Susan F. Feagin), 2001 (Box 80)
      - Office of the Executive Vice President for Research, (Fawwaz T. Ulaby), 2001 (Box 80)
      - Regents, 2001 (Box 80)
  - Annual Files, 2002
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 2002 (Box 80)
      - American Public Health Association, 2002 (Box 80)
      - Bioterrorism
        - Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Bioterrorism Center, Media, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Bioterrorism Initiative Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box 80)
          - General, 2002 (Box 80)
          - Meeting, September 26th, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Bioterrorism Proposal, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Bioterrorism Research Initiative, 2002; 2 folders (Box 80)
        - Center for Bioterrorism, 2002General (Box 80)
        - General, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Grant Documentation, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Martin, Jennifer, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Preparedness Center, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Steering Committee, 2002 (Box 80)
      - Communications, Terri Mellow, 2002 (Box 96)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2032 ]
      - Community-Based Public Health, 2002 (Box 80)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 2002 (Box 80)
        - General
          - A-E, 2002 (Box 80)
          - F-K, 2002 (Box 80)
          - L-Q, 2002 (Box 80)
          - R-Z, 2002 (Box 80)
        - Foreign, 2002 (Box 80)
      - Development Office
        - General, 2002; 2 folders (Box 80)
        - Dean's Advisory Council, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Alumni Board of Governors, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Events
        - Public Health Symposium, September 30, 2002 (Box 81)
        - SPH Faculty Retreat, April 24, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Faculty
        - Alexander, Jeff, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Merit Review, 2002 (Box 96)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Public Health Information Services and Access, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Prevention Research Center, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Recruitment, 2002 (Box 96)
      - Students, 2002 (Box 96)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2077 ]
      - Web Development, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Committees (Box 81)
      - Executive Committee, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Faculty Meetings, 2002 (Box 81)
      - General, 2002 (Box 81)
      - SPH Strategic Planning Committee, 2002 (Box 81)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Kalbfleisch, John, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Vincent, James, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Kaplan, George, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 2002 (Box 81)
        - James, Sherman, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Wessert, Bill, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - Center for Population Planning, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Interdepartmental Concentration in Genetics Director Search, 2002 (Box 81)
        - Interdepartmental Concentration in Global Health, 2002 (Box 81)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service (includes Center for Disease Control correspondence), 2002 (Box 81)
    - University
      - Academic Program Group Research Subcommittee, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Interdepartmental Concentration in Organizational Studies Seminar, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Health Sciences Council, 2002 (Box 81)
      - Health Services Research Initiative, 2002 (Box 81)